- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain!
孩子们：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
kids:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
孩子们：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
kids: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
孩子们：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
All:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
[flute plays]
[长笛演奏]
[whimsical music]
[异想天开的音乐]
♪ ♪
- Hello. I am Hans.
- 你好。我是汉斯。
And welcome
to Fishy Fairy Tales.
并欢迎
到鱼腥童话。
Now where were we?
现在我们在哪里？
Oh, yes. Here.
哦是的。这里。
Mm-hmm.
[coughs]
嗯嗯。
[咳嗽]
Und now for a classic fairy tale
现在就来听听经典童话故事吧
called "Snow Yellow
und the Seven Jellies."
名为“雪黄”
和七只果冻。”
"Once upon a time, there was
a happy little prince,
“从前，有一个
一个快乐的小王子，
and his name was Snow Yellow."
他的名字叫黄雪。”
- Hi.
Whoa!
- 你好。
哇！
- Whoopsie-daisy.
- 百日菊。
Get back in there, you cuckoo.
回到那里吧，你这个杜鹃。
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
- "Prince Snow Yellow lived
in a castle
——《黄雪王子住过》
在一座城堡里
with Queen Karen,
his evil Step-Motherboard."
与凯伦女王一起，
- I'm the villain in this story.
- 我是这个故事中的反派。
Ain't that a hoot?
[cackles]
这不是胡闹吗？
[咯咯笑]
[thunder claps]
[雷鸣般的掌声]
- Our story begins
on a beautiful day
- 我们的故事开始了
在美好的一天
just like any other.
就像其他人一样。
- [humming] [clams cooing]
- [嗡嗡声] [蛤蜊咕咕叫]
- Good morning,
my loyal subjects.
- 早上好，
我忠诚的臣民。
[townsfolk screaming]
[镇民尖叫]
[laughs]
I love you all.
[笑]
我爱你们所有人。
♪ Nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
Here are some priceless
royal jewels for you...
这里有一些无价的
皇家珠宝为您...
- [babbles]
- And you.
- [胡言乱语]
- 还有你。
- Huh.
- And you and you.
- 嗯。
- 还有你和你。
- [honks] Mm.
- [按喇叭] 嗯。
- [gulps] Ah.
- [吞咽]啊。
- ♪ Nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[sputtering]
[溅射]
Hellooo, Wishing Well!
你好，祝好！
- Hellooo, Wishing Well!
- 你好，祝好！
- Ready for our morning duet?
- 准备好我们早上的二重唱了吗？
- ♪ I-I-I'm ready ♪
- ♪ 我-我-我准备好了 ♪
- Ahem.
- 咳咳。
♪ I'm a well-wisher ♪
♪ 我是一个善良的人 ♪
- ♪ I'm a well-wisher ♪
- ♪ 我是一个祝福者 ♪
- ♪ Wishing you well ♪
- ♪ 祝你一切顺利 ♪
- ♪ Wishing Well? ♪
- ♪ 许愿井？ ♪
- ♪ Yes? ♪
- ♪ 是吗？ ♪
- ♪ I wish you
both: ♪ Well ♪
- ♪ 我祝愿你
两人：♪ 嗯 ♪
- ♪ I wish you well ♪
- ♪ 祝你一切顺利 ♪
♪ Wishes of wishing you well
- [groans]
♪ 祝你一切顺利
- [呻吟]
- ♪ Wishes
of wishing you well ♪
- ♪ 愿望
祝你一切顺利♪
- [grunts]
- ♪ I wish you well ♪
- [咕哝]
- ♪ 祝你一切顺利 ♪
♪ Wishes of wishing you
- [groans]
♪ 祝愿你
- [呻吟]
both: ♪ Wishing you ♪
两人：♪ 祝愿你 ♪
- Ouch.
- 哎哟。
- Snow Yellow!
- 雪黄！
No singing until
I've had my morning update!
直到没有唱歌
我早上更新了！
[beeping, buzzing]
[嘟嘟声，嗡嗡声]
Ah, forget it.
啊，算了。
- Oh.
- 哦。
Sorry, Queen Stepmommy.
对不起，女王继母。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
Where is she getting all
of these glass shoes?
她从哪里得到所有
这些玻璃鞋？
- Hey, Prince!
- 嘿，王子！
Start scrubbing
those royal commodes,
开始擦洗
那些皇家马桶，
or you don't eat today.
或者你今天不吃饭。
- Yay, toilet duty!
- 耶，厕所值班！
- Say, why do you look
so square all of a sudden?
- 说吧，你为什么看着
突然这么方？
[beeping]
[嘟嘟声]
- My big boy edges just grew in.
- 我的大男孩边缘刚刚长出来。
Thanks for noticing.
感谢您的关注。
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
- Oh!
- 哦！
♪ Bye, Queen Stepmommy ♪
♪ 再见，女王继母 ♪
- Ugh!
- 呃！
[wheels squeaking]
[车轮吱吱作响]
Magic mirror on my wall,
我墙上的魔镜，
who's the squarest of them all?
他们中谁是最方的？
- You, my Queen,
are square, 'tis true.
- 你，我的女王，
是正方形的，这是真的。
But Snow Yellow is the squarest,
但雪黄是最方的，
uh, boop-boop-bee-doo.
呃，噗噗噗。
- [groans] I knew it!
- [呻吟]我就知道！
- No, you didn't.
- 不，你没有。
You didn't know anything
until I told...
你什么都不知道
直到我告诉...
what?
什么？
- [grumbles]
- [抱怨]
If I wanna stay
the squarest in the land,
如果我想留下来
陆地上最方形的地方，
I need to de-squarify
Prince Snow Yellow.
我需要去方形化
黄雪王子。
But how?
但如何呢？
[video game music]
- [gasps]
[视频游戏音乐]
- [喘气]
Aah!
啊啊！
[sobbing]
[抽泣]
- Oh. That works for me.
- 哦。这对我有用。
Huntsman?
猎人？
- Hmm.
- 唔。
- Huntsman?
- [gasps]
- 亨斯迈？
- [喘气]
My Queen doth summon me!
我的女王召唤我了！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[gasping]
[喘气]
You called for my personage...
mwah, mwah...
你召唤了我的人物...
呜呜呜……
my most... mwah... perfectly square
Royal Highness?
我最...哇...完全方形
太子殿下？
- You are to take the Prince
into the forest
- 你要带走王子
进入森林
and snip off his square corners.
并剪掉他的方角。
- Aah!
But, my Queen,
- 啊啊！
但是，我的女王，
I could never
do something like that.
我永远不能
做类似的事情。
I'm a truffle hunter,
not a sponge slicer.
我是一名松露猎人，
不是海绵切片机。
- Okay then.
- 好吧。
I'll cut off your corners!
我会砍掉你的棱角！
- Aah! Aah! Aah!
- 啊啊！啊啊！啊啊！
- [gulps]
- [吞咽]
Would you like
those sponge corners
你愿意吗
那些海绵角
thick cut or deli sliced?
厚切还是熟食切片？
- Gooooo!
- 咕咕！
- Yes, my Queen!
[shrieking]
- 是的，我的女王！
[尖叫]
- Even though the task
was a pain in the rump,
- 尽管任务
臀部疼痛，
the Huntsman
pursued Snow Yellow...
猎人
追求黄雪……
- ♪ La la la la la la la
- Like a cowardly chump.
- ♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦
- 就像一个胆怯的笨蛋。
- ♪ La la la la la la la ♪
- ♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦 ♪
♪ La la la la la la
- [gasping]
♪ 啦啦啦啦啦啦
- [喘气]
Moderate thy haste, my Prince.
节制你的匆忙，我的王子。
You're frolicking too fast.
你玩得太快了
I cannot keep up.
我跟不上。
- Uh-oh.
- 呃哦。
Looks like someone skipped
their second breakfast.
好像有人跳过了
他们的第二份早餐。
Let me look in my satchel here.
让我看看我的书包里。
[menacing music]
[威胁性音乐]
- [laughs darkly] [bell dings]
- [阴暗地笑] [铃声]
[gasps]
- Here we go.
[喘气]
- 开始吧。
A royal Krabby Patty
皇家蟹黄饼
on a golden platter.
在金盘上。
[angelic vocalizing]
[天使般的声音]
- [groans dreamily]
- [梦幻般的呻吟]
- And it's all for you.
- 这一切都是为了你。
[horn blares]
- You're too kind to mutilate.
[喇叭声]
- 你太仁慈了，不会残害他人。
I can't do it!
我做不到！
- Oh, uh,
- 哦，呃，
how about with cheese?
搭配奶酪怎么样？
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- 不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
You don't understand.
你不明白。
The Queen wants me
to cut off your corners
女王想要我
切断你的角落
so she can be the squarest
in the land.
这样她就可以成为最方的
在这片土地上。
- [screams] What?
- [尖叫] 什么？
Why?
为什么？
Where?
在哪里？
When?
什么时候？
La la la la la la la la la la!
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦！
Nuh-uhhhh!
嗯嗯！
[gasps]
[喘气]
- Run, my sweet Prince.
- 奔跑吧，我可爱的王子。
Hide in the woods
and never come back!
躲进树林里
并且永远不会回来！
Leave thy Krabby Patty, though.
不过，留下你的蟹肉饼吧。
Run!
跑步！
[wails]
[哀号]
Run!
跑步！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
I don't wanna be round.
我不想变成圆的
I want to stay square!
我想保持方形！
[thunder crashing]
[雷霆轰鸣]
[wolves howling]
What?
[狼嚎]
什么？
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Oh.
哦。
Wahhh!
哇哦！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Whoa!
哇！
Huh?
啊？
[gasps]
[喘气]
Oh, no!
哦，不！
The deep dark woods!
幽深幽暗的树林！
[horn honks]
Aw.
[喇叭鸣响]
噢。
They're not that scary
as long as you...
他们没那么可怕
只要你...
[evil laughter]
[邪恶的笑声]
[screams]
[尖叫声]
[creatures growling,
chainsaw whirring]
[生物咆哮，
电锯呼呼地响]
Aah!
啊啊！
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
Yaaah!
呀啊！
My, what a cute little hive.
天啊，多么可爱的小蜂巢啊。
Maybe I can hive in the hide.
也许我可以躲在隐蔽处。
Or hide in the... hive in the...
或者躲在……蜂巢里……
hide for a while.
躲一会儿。
Hello?
你好？
Is anybody home?
有人在家吗？
I need some eyes on the inside
我需要一些观察内心的眼睛
to make sure it's safe.
以确保其安全。
[blows] Come on, baby.
[吹]来吧，宝贝。
Papa needs a new place to live.
爸爸需要一个新的住处。
Bam!
嘭！
Wow, it looks like
tiny people live here.
哇，看起来像
小人物住在这里。
It's so cute but such a mess.
它是如此可爱，但如此混乱。
- [snarling]
- [咆哮]
Ah.
啊。
Mon cherie.
Ho-ho-ho.
蒙切丽。
嗬嗬嗬。
- Oh, no, you don't.
- 哦，不，你不知道。
I'm gonna need these.
我需要这些。
[gulps]
[吞咽]
Aww, seven little chairs,
each with a name.
哇，七把小椅子，
每个都有一个名字。
But this place is a dump.
但这地方是个垃圾场。
It's really a shame.
实在是太可惜了。
It would make
a perfect hideaway.
这将使
一个完美的世外桃源。
Say, maybe if I clean it,
说吧，也许如果我把它清理干净，
they'll let me stay.
他们会让我留下来。
Hooray!
万岁！
Toilet duty!
厕所值班！
♪ Now there's just one thing,
with a ring-a-ding-ding ♪
♪ 现在只有一件事，
伴随着“叮叮叮”的响声♪
♪ To get in the swing
while you work, you... ♪
♪ 荡起秋千
当你工作的时候，你...♪
[creatures warbling]
[生物的鸣叫]
That's right... warble!
没错……颤抖！
[warbling]
[颤音]
[all warbling]
[全部颤抖]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[straining]
[紧张]
Oh, well.
那好吧。
If it gets tough
and your energy is sapped,
如果事情变得艰难
而你的能量被耗尽，
sometimes it's best
to take a nap.
有时这是最好的
小睡一下。
- [laughs deviously]
- [狡猾地笑]
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
- "While the Prince
took a quick nappy-poo,
——“虽然王子
快速尿布便便，
"the seven jellies who live
“活着的七只水母
in the hive were happily
at work."
在蜂巢里快乐地
在工作中。”
[jellies buzzing happily]
[果冻高兴地嗡嗡作响]
♪ ♪
[together] ♪ We mine
flowers of the sea ♪
[一起] ♪ 我们开采
海里的花♪
♪ So we can make sweet jelly ♪
♪ 这样我们就可以制作甜果冻了 ♪
- ♪ And I can make me money ♪
- ♪ 我可以赚钱 ♪
- ♪ This pollen
sure smells funny ♪
- ♪ 这个花粉
确实闻起来很有趣♪
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
[jellies buzzing happily]
[果冻高兴地嗡嗡作响]
Aah!
啊啊！
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[all groan]
[全都呻吟]
- Hmm?
- Meow.
- 唔？
- 喵。
- Ow!
- Eek!
- 噢！
- 哎呀！
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
[groans]
- [laughs]
[呻吟]
- [笑]
- Meow?
- Huh?
- 喵？
- 啊？
[laughter]
[笑声]
[clock chimes]
[钟声]
- [cuckoos]
Stop working, ya morons.
- [杜鹃]
别再工作了，你们这些白痴。
It's 5:00!
5:00 了！
[spits]
[bell dings]
[吐口水]
[铃声]
Bingo!
宾果！
- Woo-hoo!
- Hurray!
- 呜呼！
- 万岁！
- Whoo-hoo!
- Yahoo!
- 呼呼！
- 雅虎！
- Whoo-hoo!
- Ho-ho!
- 呼呼！
- 嗬嗬！
[jellies buzzing happily]
[果冻高兴地嗡嗡作响]
- "When the seven jellies
got home..."
——《当七个果冻
到家了……”
[alarm blares]
both: Aah!
[警报声]
两人：啊啊！
- "They did not expect to find
- “他们没想到会发现
a snoring monster
in their kitchen."
打鼾的怪物
在他们的厨房里。”
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- Attack!
- 攻击！
All: Yeah!
全体：是啊！
- [snores]
- [打鼾]
[mutters dazedly]
[creatures gasp]
[茫然地嘀咕]
[生物喘息]
[all gasp, groan]
[全都喘息，呻吟]
- Whoo!
- 呼！
How do you...
[exclaiming] Do?
你怎么...
[惊呼]做吗？
You must be the owners of
this lovely little hive.
您必须是
这个可爱的小蜂巢。
- That's right.
My name is...
- 这是正确的。
我的名字是...
- No, don't tell me.
- 不，别告诉我。
I saw your names
on your adorable little chairs.
我看到了你们的名字
在你可爱的小椅子上。
Let me guess.
让我猜一下。
You must be Nutty.
你一定是个疯子。
- Yee-haw!
- 哎呀！
You hit the bull's-eye there.
你击中了靶心。
- And you're Krusty!
- 你是库斯蒂！
[chimes jangle]
[钟声叮当]
- Jackpot!
[chortles]
- 大奖！
[咯咯笑]
- Op.
- Puffy.
- 操作。
- 浮肿。
- That is correct.
- 这是正确的。
- Dummy.
- 假的。
- Duuuh.
- 呃。
- Gimme that.
- 给我那个。
Cooty.
傻瓜。
- You're darn tootin'!
- 你太他妈的了！
[chuckles]
[笑声]
Aah!
啊啊！
- Meow.
- And Gary.
- 喵。
- 还有加里。
- Meow.
- 喵。
- The question is, who are you?
- 问题是，你是谁？
And what are you doing
in our house?
你在做什么
在我们家？
- And you must be
- 你一定是
Drippy.
滴水。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
Nice to... [groaning]
Meet ya.
很高兴...[呻吟]
遇见你。
I'm Snow Yellow.
我是雪黄
[jellies gasp]
both: Snow Yellow?
[果冻喘气]
两人：雪黄？
- The Prince?
- 王子？
- Yes, and I'm
in a dangerous pickle.
- 是的，我是
在危险的泡菜中。
It all started when...
一切都开始于……
- Pickle?
- 泡菜？
- It all started when...
mirror!
- 一切都开始于……
镜子！
- "While the Prince tells..."
- Snip! Snip!
- “当王子告诉……”
- 剪断！剪断！
- "His harrowing story
to the jellies,
- “他的悲惨故事
对于果冻来说，
"the Huntsman was feeding lies
to the Queen
“猎人在撒谎
致女王
"about cutting off
the Prince's corners.
“关于切断
王子的角落。
And she ate it up
with great relish."
然后她就把它吃掉了
津津有味。”
- Magic mirror on the wall,
- 墙上的魔镜，
now who's the squarest one of...
现在谁是最方形的...
- Save your breath.
- 省点口气。
The Prince is still square.
太子还是方正的。
- What?
- 什么？
- The Huntsman is lying,
- 猎人在撒谎，
if you weren't aware.
如果你不知道的话。
- Lying?
- 撒谎？
I have never been
so offended in my...
我从来没有去过
如此冒犯了我的...
[shrieks]
[尖叫声]
[knives shinging]
[刀光闪闪]
Uh, who are you gonna believe,
呃，你会相信谁，
me or some loopy looking glass?
我还是一些疯狂的镜子？
- I believe you, of course.
- 我当然相信你。
- Phew.
- 唷。
- I believe
you're alligator bait.
- 我相信
你是鳄鱼的诱饵。
- Huh? Wah!
- 啊？哇！
No! No!
不！不！
[alligator chomping]
No! Aah!
[鳄鱼咀嚼]
不！啊啊！
[whimpering]
[呜咽]
- If you want someone cut right,
- 如果你想让某人正确，
you have to cut 'em yourself.
你必须自己剪。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
The Prince will
never recognize me
王子将会
永远认不出我
in this wacky getup.
在这古怪的装扮中。
Oop.
[laughs]
哎呀。
[笑]
Uh.
呃。
[mysterious music]
[神秘的音乐]
♪ ♪
I'll dip this ball
of poison chum
我会把这个球浸入水中
毒友的
in a candy coating
that no one can resist.
在糖果涂层中
无人能抗拒。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- "So Queen Karen snuck away
- “于是凯伦女王就偷偷溜走了
to the seven jellies' hive
and"... ow!
到七只水母的蜂巢
以及“……噢！
- I can turn
my own pages, thank you.
- 我可以转身
我自己的页面，谢谢。
Ugh!
啊!
[jellies buzzing happily]
[果冻高兴地嗡嗡作响]
[light music]
[轻音乐]
- Thanks so much for letting me
crash here a while.
- 非常感谢你让我
这里崩溃了一段时间。
I'll grill jelly patties
for dinner.
我会烤果冻馅饼
吃晚饭。
[all cheer]
[大家欢呼]
[jellies buzzing happily]
[果冻高兴地嗡嗡作响]
Goodbye. See ya tonight.
再见。今晚见。
- Meow.
- Uh...
- 喵。
- 呃...
[groaning]
[呻吟]
I'll miss you too, Gary.
我也会想念你的，加里。
- Meow-meow.
- 喵喵。
♪ Mow-mow-mow, mow-mow-mow ♪
♪ 喵——喵——喵，喵——喵——喵 ♪
- Peekaboo!
- [screams]
- 躲猫猫！
- [尖叫]
- Hello,
my sickeningly square friend.
- 你好，
我那令人作呕的方方正正的朋友。
May I use your restroom?
我可以使用你的洗手间吗？
- Of course.
- 当然。
I'm sure
the jellies wouldn't mind.
我确定
果冻不会介意。
[humming]
[toilet flushes]
[嗡嗡声]
[厕所冲水]
- I see you've made
a delicious dinner.
- 我看到你已经做到了
一顿美味的晚餐。
Can I interest you
in a mouthwatering chum ball
我可以让你感兴趣吗
在令人垂涎欲滴的密友球中
to go with that?
去那个？
- Whoa. Eee.
- 哇哦。呃。
Thank you, kind crone.
谢谢你，好心的老太婆。
But I don't like chum.
但我不喜欢密友。
- But my chum balls
are dipped in candy.
-但是我的好朋友
都浸在糖果里。
Ooh.
哦。
Num-num-num-num-num.
数-数-数-数-数。
Mmm, chummy.
[giggles]
嗯，亲密。
[咯咯笑]
Hey?
嘿？
- Oh, I guess
a little nibble wouldn't hurt.
- 哦，我想
咬一点不会痛的。
[gulps] Hey.
[吞咽]嘿。
That actually
tastes pretty good.
那实际上
味道还不错。
- Now you'll be
in a dehydrated sleep forever.
- 现在你会是
永远处于脱水的睡眠中。
And I'll be the squarest
in the land.
我会是最正直的
在这片土地上。
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
- ♪ Buzz-buzz-buzz,
buzz-buzz-buzz ♪
- ♪ 嗡嗡嗡嗡，
嗡嗡嗡嗡♪
Duh, forgot my pickax.
呃，忘了我的镐了。
Huh?
啊？
An evil witch?
邪恶的女巫？
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- Duh, wait a minute.
- 呃，等一下。
Pricey hairband,
昂贵的发带，
removable snoot,
可拆卸束光筒，
party hat?
派对帽？
You're not an evil witch.
你不是邪恶的女巫。
[alarm blares]
You're an evil queen!
[警报声]
你是一个邪恶的女王！
- Keep quiet, you fool!
- 保持安静，你这个傻瓜！
- [chomps]
- Aah! Get back here!
- [咀嚼]
- 啊啊！回到这里！
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
Duhhhh!
呵呵！
[jellies buzzing happily]
[果冻高兴地嗡嗡作响]
[all groaning]
[全都呻吟]
[together] The Queen?
[合] 女王？
- Snow Yellow is in trouble!
- 黄雪有麻烦了！
- Meow!
- 喵！
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, aah!
- 哇，哇，哇，啊！
[all whining worriedly]
[大家都担心地抱怨]
- Whoa!
- 哇！
All: Snow Yellow?
全体：雪黄？
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
- The Queen dried him out.
- 女王把他擦干了。
And I think she ate
all our jelly patties!
而且我认为她吃了
我们所有的果冻馅饼！
[burps]
[打嗝]
Bad Queen went that-a-way.
坏女王就是这么做的。
- Let's hog-tie
that royal pain in the caboose.
- 让我们打成平手
守车里那种皇家般的痛苦。
♪ ♪
[siren wails]
Aah!
[警报声]
啊啊！
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- 哇，哇，哇。
- I have to get away
from those jelly brains.
- 我必须离开
来自那些果冻大脑。
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
[all snarling]
[全都咆哮]
- See ya in the next fairy tale.
- 下一个童话故事见。
♪ ♪
[cackles]
[咯咯笑]
[jellies yelling angrily]
[果冻愤怒地大喊]
[both roar]
[双方怒吼]
- Yah!
Uh!
- 啊！
呃！
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- [screaming gibberish]
- [尖叫着胡言乱语]
[groans]
[呻吟]
- Whoa! Whoa, magic mirror
on the wall...
- 哇！哇哦，魔镜
在墙上...
- All right.
- 好的。
You're the squarest...
jumpin' jellies!
你是最方的...
跳跃的果冻！
- Huh?
[all snarling]
- 啊？
[全都咆哮]
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
Nyah! Time to hit
my escape key.
呀！击球时间
我的逃生键。
[all scream]
[所有人尖叫]
- Aah! Story time's over.
- 啊啊！故事时间结束了。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Why did I put in stairs?
我为什么要加楼梯？
Ugh!
[jellies shouting indistinctly]
啊!
[果冻含糊不清地喊叫]
[gasps]
[喘气]
[thunder rumbles]
[whimpers]
[雷声隆隆]
[呜咽]
Aah! Aah!
啊啊！啊啊！
[suspenseful music]
[悬疑音乐]
Uh...
呃...
[buzzing]
[嗡嗡声]
- Gotcha.
- Uh, no.
- 明白了。
- 呃，不。
I've got you!
我有你！
Time to mush these jellies
into marmalade.
是时候把这些果冻捣碎了
变成果酱。
[all gasp]
[全都喘气]
[epic music]
[史诗音乐]
all: Ah!
众人：啊！
- [cackles]
- [咯咯笑]
Screwdrivers?
螺丝刀？
Wha... what are you doing?
什……你在做什么？
[jellies mumbling indistinctly]
[果冻含糊不清地咕哝]
Not my screws!
不是我的螺丝！
- Magic mirror off the wall,
- 墙上的魔镜，
who's the fastest one of all?
谁是最快的？
♪ Me ♪
♪ 我 ♪
[chuckles]
[brick whistling]
[笑声]
[砖头呼啸声]
Oh, great.
哦，太好了。
Seven years bad luck.
七年运气不好。
Ugh.
啊。
- Oh!
- 哦！
I was the squarest.
我是最方的。
Oh, what a world.
噢，多么美好的世界啊。
[sobs]
[抽泣]
- Well then. Cannot turn
the page now, can you?
- 那么。无法转动
现在页面可以吗？
"While still under
the Queen's sleeping spell,
“虽然还在
女王的沉睡咒语，
"the seven jellies placed
the Prince in a sponge dish
“七个果冻放在
海绵盘里的王子
to keep him
from getting moldy."
留住他
以免发霉。”
[all crying]
[都哭了]
[all sobbing]
[全都抽泣]
- [wails]
- [哀号]
[both sob]
[两人都抽泣]
- [crying]
- [哭泣]
- Meow!
- 喵！
- I'm ready!
- 我准备好了！
All: Hooray!
全体：万岁！
[all gasp in horror]
[所有人都惊恐地倒吸一口冷气]
- Snow Yellow?
- 雪黄？
You're still alive!
你还活着！
- And naked. Eee.
- 还有裸体。呃。
- I sure am.
- 我当然是。
You little jellies
saved my... whoa!
你们这些小果冻
救了我的……哇！
- EH, put these on, boy-o.
- 呃，穿上这些，男孩。
- Oh. Thanks, Krusty.
- 哦。谢谢，库斯蒂。
You little jellies
saved my sponge.
你们这些小果冻
救了我的海绵。
- You're darn tootin'.
- 你太他妈的了。
We took that rotten Queen
apart... bolt by bolt.
我们带走了那个腐烂的女王
分开……一点一点地分开。
She won't bother you no more.
她不会再打扰你了。
[laughs]
[笑]
- In that case,
- 在这种情况下，
you can all crash at my hive.
你们都可以冲进我的蜂巢。
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
all: Hooray.
全体：万岁。
Aww.
[crackling]
哇。
[爆裂声]
[sizzling]
[嘶嘶声]
- Hooray!
- 万岁！
- [cheering]
- [欢呼]
- A-one, two, three, four.
- A-一、二、三、四。
[bright music]
[明亮的音乐]
[gentle string music]
[轻柔的弦乐]
♪ ♪
- Whoo!
- 呼！
[giggles]
[咯咯笑]
- [chuckles]
- [轻笑]
[together] ♪ Buzz-buzz-buzz,
buzz-buzz-buzz ♪
[一起]♪ 嗡嗡嗡嗡，
嗡嗡嗡嗡♪
♪ Buzz-buzz-buzz,
buzz-buzz-buzz ♪
♪ 嗡嗡嗡嗡，
嗡嗡嗡嗡♪
- Huzzah!
- 好啊！
[together] ♪ Buzz-buzz-buzz
- Whoo! [laughs]
[一起]♪ 嗡嗡嗡嗡
- 呼！ [笑]
[all buzzing happily]
[大家都高兴地嗡嗡作响]
[together] ♪ Buzz-buzz-buzz,
buzz-buzz-buzz ♪
[一起]♪ 嗡嗡嗡嗡，
嗡嗡嗡嗡♪
- [vocalizes]
- [发声]
- [vomits]
- [呕吐]
- [laughs]
- [笑]
[cheering]
[欢呼]
- Yes, indeed.
- 是的，确实如此。
"And they all lived
happily ever"...
“他们都住过
永远幸福”...
ow! My finger!
噢！我的手指！
[whimpering]
[呜咽]